So hey friends welcome back to another new
video friends in today's video I am going to tell you
how you can download your Ayman card from LKR
you all know it is such a way in which all the
documents are kept through the government,
all your documents are
saved in it, consider it as your physical
wallet and a LKR is the same, so
you can also keep your Ayman card in that LKR,
how can you download it,
in today's video I am going to tell you the complete process,
in the previous video I
taught you how to download the application,
in this I am going to tell you how to add you to the LKR, so the
video will continue, do
watch the video till the end, so let's start
friends after it appears on your mobile screen, first of all
you have to go to Play
Store, there you have to search for LKR,
okay on LKR you have to
create an account first, okay
you have to create an account with the same mobile number
which is used in all your documents  It is
linked to the Aadhaar card, the main
important thing is that it is linked to the Aadhaar card, okay, so
I opened it here, Dig Locker is
taking some time to open,
so look here, you will get such an interface,
Dig Load, this will be your profile,
your Aadhaar card must be linked in it, first of all,
if you are
logging in for the first time, then first of all you have to
save your Aadhaar card in it,
okay, after saving the Aadhaar card,
look here, you will go to search,
search for document, okay, here you will enter health,
okay, after entering health,
look here, you do not have to enter the National Health ID card, you have to
enter
Pradhan Mantri Jan Arogya Yojana here because
your Ayushman card has been approved,
okay, but you have to
download it, okay, so
in today's video I am going to tell you
how to do it from the locker, okay, the rest
you can do from the site as well as
from the application, okay, so
what is in the locker here remains the same, Dig Locker
documents are valid everywhere.
Okay, you can show the DigiLocker anywhere, the
documents of physical and DigiLocker are the
same, okay, so look here,
you will have to enter your PMG ID
here, the rest of the
details will be fetched automatically here, okay,
see the name from Aadhaar which is your
name in the Aadhaar card and the
date of birth in your Aadhaar card will come here, here
you people have to enter the PMG ID and
see here select the state name, okay,
here you people have to select the state
from which you
are, so see here I have selected the state,
okay, now I am
entering your PMG ID here, so if you are facing any problem while entering the PMG ID, then
please tell me
in the comment, I will tell you about it,
okay, so here I enter my PMG
ID and click on get document, so
look here I have entered the PMG ID,
okay, check the rest of the details also,
your name, date of birth and PMG
ID and here the state name, whatever date
of birth is there, it is mandatory here.  I have
filled everything, you have to give consent here,
consent has been given automatically, okay, so
look here, when you click on get document, then
see here your Ayushman
card will be downloaded here, so see
here the Pradhan Mantri Jan Arogya Yojana is
fetching your Ayushman card
from the National Health Authority, okay,
look here, please wait for some time,
so look here, in all my
documents, I have my class 10 marksheet,
PAN verification is also there, my Aadhar card is
also in it, so look here, Pradhan Mantri Jan
Arogya Yojana which is Ayushman Bharat,
my card is here, free treatment of Rs 5 lakh,
see here the Ayushman card, okay, which has been
downloaded in it, so
look here, your Ayushman card will be visible here,
okay, if you
get treatment anywhere, you can show it here
or you can show the physical one as well, both are the same,
okay, the documents that
you take a photo of, it is a
different matter, okay, that is not very valid,
photoshot is okay and screenshot but
your Digi Locker  The documents verified through DigiLocker are the same,
they are verified through the government, the
physical card and the
document downloaded in DigiLocker are both the same, both of them are
valid, okay, because DigiLocker is
a government-issued application in
which all the documents are correct,
okay, so by following these steps
you can download this card
from the locker, so hope you guys liked the video, if you liked the
video then like it and
share it with as many people as possible
so that those people too can
easily download the Ayushman card from the locker and
I have made a complete video of the dealer, if
you want to know in depth about the dealer,
what is the level, I will tell you
in the video but I will tell you in a short way,
but I have made a complete video, so I will
give the link of that video in the description, so you can watch it from there,
and I
make a playlist for everything, like I
work for EPFO, most of the videos are of my
EPFO ​​because I am an EPFO  I
make videos about this,
so I have made videos for EPF as well and you will get
playlists for Aadhar and Ayman card as well, so go to the channel and
keep checking the playlist, I keep
updating it daily, I hope you
guys liked the video, so you guys
must subscribe to the channel because
by subscribing you get my support
so that I can keep making videos for you, so
that's all for today, till the next video, bye guys